<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anders Sjørslev Schmidt on Anders Sjørslev Schmidt</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anders Sjørslev Schmidt on Anders Sjørslev Schmidt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardioversion of atrial fibrillation - Can we predict success using copeptin?</title>
      <link>/post/copeptin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/copeptin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P02.07 PhD Day 2019, Aarhus University:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cardioversion of atrial fibrillation: Can we predict success using copeptin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study aims to investigate if successful outcome after
electrical direct current cardioversion of atrial fibrillation can be predicted
based on the biomarker copeptin. Cardioversion is an important treatment
option, which aims to reduce disease burden. However, cardioversion is
not always successful, and recurrence of atrial fibrillation is present in 50-
80% of patients after one year. Copeptin is a novel biomarker associated
with cardiovascular morbidity. In this study, we aimed to investigate the association between copeptin and outcomes after cardioversion of atrial fibrillation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patients undergoing elective cardioversion of atrial fibrillation
were included. The level of copeptin was determined before
cardioversion and at 90-day follow-up. The data are a post-hoc analysis of &lt;a href=&#34;https://andersschmidt.netlify.com/publication/jaha-study/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a previous study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In total, 116 patients were included of which 85 (73 %) were male.
The baseline characteristics were not statistically significantly different between patients with
successful or failed cardioversion outcome with the exception of the  left atrial volume, as patients with a successful cardioversion had a smaller left atrium size (p=0.03), a tendency that persisted after correction for
the body surface area (indexed left atrial volume), p=0.05 (Table 1):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/table1.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Baseline characteristics&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data on cardioversion outcome is presented in
Table 2. Furthermore, as we have demonstrated in &lt;a href=&#34;https://andersschmidt.netlify.com/publication/jaha-study/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a previous study&lt;/a&gt;, the two defibrillators were of different efficacy, and accordingly, data on cardioversion outcome is reported stratified by defibrillator in Table 2. Data on the follow-up outcomes are presented in Table 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/table2_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Figure 1 we present the biomarker data using boxplots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/figure1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Fig 1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This study was an observational study on data collected from a randomized trial with a modest sample
size. Our population consisted of patients with persistent atrial fibrillation with a longer-term duration and
thus represents more severe cases of AF. Therefore, the results should be interpreted with caution in other
AF populations. Copeptin levels vary slightly between genders in the general population. However, we did
not stratify for gender in the study as the proportion of males and females were similar in patients with and
without successful cardioversion. In the study we used simple stratification and comparison of biomarker levels; however, a binary regression model enabling adjustment for known confounders may be useful in further analyses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/strong&gt;
Copeptin levels were not associated with the outcome after cardioverting atrial fibrillation. We also found no
association  between  copeptin  levels  at  follow-up  in  patients  presenting  with  sinus  rhythm  and  atrial
fibrillation respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug repurposing: A talk by James Harrison, Cycle Pharma</title>
      <link>/post/drug-repurposing-a-talk-by-james-harrison-cycle-pharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/drug-repurposing-a-talk-by-james-harrison-cycle-pharma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;James Harrison is excecutive chairman of Cycle Pharmaceuticals, a company based on an exiting idea: Using well-known mediccations for new purposes &amp;ldquo;re-purposing&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tableone package: Effiencent Table 1&#39;s for clinical studies</title>
      <link>/post/the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every randomized study need a Table 1 to summarize the characteristics of the included participants. The tables consist of multiple calculations of means with standard deviation, medians with quartiles or summarizes of categorical variables. This can however be very time consuming to calculate if done &lt;em&gt;by hard&lt;/em&gt;. Especially, because you often want to make several subgroups etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some years ago I came across the &lt;em&gt;R&lt;/em&gt; package &lt;em&gt;tableone&lt;/em&gt;, which has now become my preffered tool for creating &lt;em&gt;table 1’s&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, the package must be installed and loaded into a &lt;em&gt;R&lt;/em&gt; session:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;#Install &amp;quot;tableone&amp;quot;, if not already installed and loaded:
if (!require(&amp;quot;tableone&amp;quot;)) install.packages(&amp;quot;tableone&amp;quot;); library(tableone)
#I also like to use the tidyverse packages to plot and analyse the data:
if (!require(&amp;quot;tidyverse&amp;quot;)) install.packages(&amp;quot;tidyverse&amp;quot;); library(tidyverse)

#Load some sample data, here the &amp;quot;iris&amp;quot; data set, or use your own data set:
data(&amp;quot;iris&amp;quot;)
attach(iris)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the data set and determine how you would like to analyse the different variables. Use histograms, QQ-plots etc. to investigate the variables. The &lt;strong&gt;iris&lt;/strong&gt; data consist of 5 different variables, four are continous (length and width) and one is a categorical (species).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;a &amp;lt;- ggplot(iris, aes(iris$Sepal.Width)) + geom_histogram() + theme_classic()
a + labs(x= &amp;quot;Sepal Width&amp;quot;, y=&amp;quot;&amp;quot;, title = &amp;quot;Sample plot&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2018-08-10-the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies_files/figure-html/unnamed-chunk-2-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;ggplot(iris) + geom_qq(aes(sample = iris$Sepal.Width)) + theme_classic() + labs( x = &amp;quot;Sepal Width&amp;quot;, y=&amp;quot;&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2018-08-10-the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies_files/figure-html/unnamed-chunk-3-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;#Choose which variables to include in table 1 (NB: All variables must be listed here)
variables &amp;lt;- c(&amp;quot;Sepal.Width&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Sepal.Length&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Petal.Width&amp;quot;)
#Which of the above chosen variables must be treated as a non-normal variable?
non_normal &amp;lt;- c()

#Use the argument strata for subgroups:
mytableone &amp;lt;- tableone::CreateTableOne( data = iris, vars = variables, strata = &amp;quot;Species&amp;quot;)

#Adjust the amount of digits, use of test and more:
print(mytableone, nonnormal = non_normal, explain=TRUE, catDigits=1, contDigits=1, test=F)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;##                           Stratified by Species
##                            setosa    versicolor virginica
##   n                         50        50         50      
##   Sepal.Width (mean (sd))  3.4 (0.4) 2.8 (0.3)  3.0 (0.3)
##   Sepal.Length (mean (sd)) 5.0 (0.4) 5.9 (0.5)  6.6 (0.6)
##   Petal.Width (mean (sd))  0.2 (0.1) 1.3 (0.2)  2.0 (0.3)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Descion-tree analysis: A look on the FFTrees package</title>
      <link>/post/descion-tree-analysis-a-look-on-the-fftrees-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/descion-tree-analysis-a-look-on-the-fftrees-package/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As medical doctors we use descions tree every day. Many observations from studies have been condensed to a clinical scoring system which aid the clinican in taking descions about further investigations on a given patient.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My notes on - Effect size and sample size estimations for clinical trials</title>
      <link>/post/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On my way to design a third and fourth clinical trial I found it useful to reflect on the way the previous studies were designed and what considerations I have made. Randomized trials are only as good as they are designed - and important considerations must be made prior to the initiation of the project. Often recruitment of patients may last for years and therefore a careful plan is needed to enhance the scientific outcome of the study. Conventional randomized trials are designed so that they will provide a meaningful answer on its own (definitive stand-alone study), adresses a superiority question, allocates patients in a 1:1 ratio to two parallel study groups.(1)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;choosing-the-best-primary-endpoint&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Choosing the best primary endpoint&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the sample size estimation and the conclusion of the study is based on what was choosen as primary endpoint it is of outmost importance to deside on the primary endpoint a priori. Also, the endpoint must be meaningful to clinicians, so that the results can be implemented in practise and provide not just evidence but useful information. The primary endpoint must be a variable were it is meaningful to calculate and detect a difference, i.e. &lt;strong&gt;effect size&lt;/strong&gt;. One must deside on choosing an endpoint that is realistic to clinicians or an endpoint that is realistic to the current evidence and in-line with previous studies. Ideal the endpoint is realistic to both. As a further guidance the principe of “the minimal difference important to patients.”(2) Consequently, even a minimal difference can be relevant, when the endpoint is e.g. deaths (mortality) or major cardiovascular events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For cardioversion trials the endpoint is often “cardioversion efficacy”, i.e. the proportion of patients with a successful treatment outcome. This endpoint has many advantages and we desided on using &lt;strong&gt;cardioversion outcome&lt;/strong&gt; since it provides crusial benefits:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It a variable, were a difference can be meassured and is clinical meaningful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It a dicotomous outcome, which is very robust, and can be documented on an electrocardiogram&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, for the individual trials a taget difference must be determined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;sample-size-estimation&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Sample size estimation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For estimating the trial size I use the &lt;code&gt;power.prop.test&lt;/code&gt; function in &lt;em&gt;R&lt;/em&gt;. Considering a hypothesis where the estimated success in the control group is 85% and 95% in the experimental group, i.e. an effect size of 10%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;power.prop.test(p1 = 0.85,                      #p1 = proportion in control group
                p2 = 0.95,                      #p2 = propottion in the experimental group
                sig.level = 0.05,               #choose significance level, standard is 0.05 (alfa value)
                power = 0.80,                   #choose power (beta value)
                alternative = c(&amp;quot;two.sided&amp;quot;),   
                n = NULL
                )&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;## 
##      Two-sample comparison of proportions power calculation 
## 
##               n = 140.0951
##              p1 = 0.85
##              p2 = 0.95
##       sig.level = 0.05
##           power = 0.8
##     alternative = two.sided
## 
## NOTE: n is number in *each* group&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;references&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cook JA, Hislop J, Altman DG, et al. Specifying the target difference in the primary outcome for a randomised controlled trial: guidance for researchers. Trials. 2015;16(1). &lt;a href=&#34;doi:10.1186/s13063-014-0526-8&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;doi:10.1186/s13063-014-0526-8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beaton DE, Boers M, Wells GA. Many faces of the minimal clinically important difference (MCID): a literature review and directions for future research. Current Opinion in Rheumatology. 2002;14(2):109.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardioversion Efficacy Using Pulsed Biphasic or Biphasic Truncated Exponential Waveforms: A Randomized Clinical Trial</title>
      <link>/publication/jaha-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jaha-study/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt; Several different defibrillators are currently used for cardioversion and defibrillation of cardiac arrhythmias. The efficacy of a novel pulsed biphasic (PB) waveform has not been compared to other biphasic waveforms. Accordingly, this study aims to compare the efficacy and safety of PB shocks with biphasic truncated exponential (BTE) shocks in patients undergoing cardioversion of atrial fibrillation or ‐flutter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Methods and Results&lt;/strong&gt; This prospective, randomized study included patients admitted for elective direct current cardioversion. Patients were randomized to receive cardioversion using either PB or BTE shocks. We used escalating shocks until sinus rhythm was obtained or to a maximum of 4 shocks. Patients randomized to PB shocks received 90, 120, 150, and 200 J and patients randomized to BTE shocks received 100, 150, 200, and 250 J, as recommended by the manufacturers. In total, 69 patients (51%) received PB shocks and 65 patients (49%) BTE shocks. Successful cardioversion, defined as sinus rhythm 4 hours after cardioversion, was achieved in 43 patients (62%) using PB shocks and in 56 patients (86%) using BTE shocks; ratio 1.4 (95% CI 1.1–1.7) (P=0.002). There was no difference in safety (ie, myocardial injury judged by changes in high‐sensitive troponin I levels; ratio 1.1) (95% CI 1.0–1.3), P=0.15. The study was terminated prematurely because of an adverse event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusions&lt;/strong&gt; Cardioversion using a BTE waveform was more effective when compared with a PB waveform. There was no difference in safety between the 2 waveforms, as judged by changes in troponin I levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical Trial Registration&lt;/strong&gt; URL: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.clinicaltrials.gov&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://www.clinicaltrials.gov&lt;/a&gt;. Unique identifier: NCT02317029.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical experience and skills of physicians in hospital cardiac arrest teams in Denmark: a nationwide study</title>
      <link>/publication/clinical-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/clinical-skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of hyperoxia on myocardial injury following cardioversion—A randomized clinical trial</title>
      <link>/publication/oxy-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/oxy-study/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elevated calprotectin in patients with atrial fibrillation with and without heart failure</title>
      <link>/publication/calprotectin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/calprotectin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivational Talk: Why persue Student Research?</title>
      <link>/talk/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/motivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I will provide further details as deadline proceeds.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the PhD study</title>
      <link>/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I will provide further details as deadline proceeds.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AF48: Timing of cardioversion in new-onset atrial fibrillation</title>
      <link>/project/af48/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/af48/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background:&lt;/strong&gt; The treatment of patients with recent onset atrial fibrillation (AF) often aims for rapid restoration of sinus rhythm.  Current guidelines suggest that cardioversion can be performed safely without anticoagulation within 48 hours from symptoms onset. However, an unacceptable high risk of thromboembolism has been identified in patients with heart failure and diabetes, i.e. risk factors for stroke.
&lt;strong&gt;Aim:&lt;/strong&gt; To investigate the risk of thromboembolism after acute cardioversion versus rate control among patient with recent onset symptomatic atrial fibrillation.
&lt;strong&gt;Methods:&lt;/strong&gt; In this prospective study, patients presenting with resent onset atrial fibrillation will be screened for eligibility.
&lt;strong&gt;Hypothesis:&lt;/strong&gt; Among patients with risk factors for stroke, a rate control strategy significantly reduces the risk of thromboembolism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHESS: Cardioversion Energy Settings</title>
      <link>/project/chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/chess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Duis posuere tellus ac convallis placerat. Proin tincidunt magna sed ex sollicitudin condimentum. Sed ac faucibus dolor, scelerisque sollicitudin nisi. Cras purus urna, suscipit quis sapien eu, pulvinar tempor diam. Quisque risus orci, mollis id ante sit amet, gravida egestas nisl. Sed ac tempus magna. Proin in dui enim. Donec condimentum, sem id dapibus fringilla, tellus enim condimentum arcu, nec volutpat est felis vel metus. Vestibulum sit amet erat at nulla eleifend gravida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nullam vel molestie justo. Curabitur vitae efficitur leo. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Sed pulvinar mauris dui, eget varius purus congue ac. Nulla euismod, lorem vel elementum dapibus, nunc justo porta mi, sed tempus est est vel tellus. Nam et enim eleifend, laoreet sem sit amet, elementum sem. Morbi ut leo congue, maximus velit ut, finibus arcu. In et libero cursus, rutrum risus non, molestie leo. Nullam congue quam et volutpat malesuada. Sed risus tortor, pulvinar et dictum nec, sodales non mi. Phasellus lacinia commodo laoreet. Nam mollis, erat in feugiat consectetur, purus eros egestas tellus, in auctor urna odio at nibh. Mauris imperdiet nisi ac magna convallis, at rhoncus ligula cursus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cras aliquam rhoncus ipsum, in hendrerit nunc mattis vitae. Duis vitae efficitur metus, ac tempus leo. Cras nec fringilla lacus. Quisque sit amet risus at ipsum pharetra commodo. Sed aliquam mauris at consequat eleifend. Praesent porta, augue sed viverra bibendum, neque ante euismod ante, in vehicula justo lorem ac eros. Suspendisse augue libero, venenatis eget tincidunt ut, malesuada at lorem. Donec vitae bibendum arcu. Aenean maximus nulla non pretium iaculis. Quisque imperdiet, nulla in pulvinar aliquet, velit quam ultrices quam, sit amet fringilla leo sem vel nunc. Mauris in lacinia lacus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suspendisse a tincidunt lacus. Curabitur at urna sagittis, dictum ante sit amet, euismod magna. Sed rutrum massa id tortor commodo, vitae elementum turpis tempus. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean purus turpis, venenatis a ullamcorper nec, tincidunt et massa. Integer posuere quam rutrum arcu vehicula imperdiet. Mauris ullamcorper quam vitae purus congue, quis euismod magna eleifend. Vestibulum semper vel augue eget tincidunt. Fusce eget justo sodales, dapibus odio eu, ultrices lorem. Duis condimentum lorem id eros commodo, in facilisis mauris scelerisque. Morbi sed auctor leo. Nullam volutpat a lacus quis pharetra. Nulla congue rutrum magna a ornare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aliquam in turpis accumsan, malesuada nibh ut, hendrerit justo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Quisque sed erat nec justo posuere suscipit. Donec ut efficitur arcu, in malesuada neque. Nunc dignissim nisl massa, id vulputate nunc pretium nec. Quisque eget urna in risus suscipit ultricies. Pellentesque odio odio, tincidunt in eleifend sed, posuere a diam. Nam gravida nisl convallis semper elementum. Morbi vitae felis faucibus, vulputate orci placerat, aliquet nisi. Aliquam erat volutpat. Maecenas sagittis pulvinar purus, sed porta quam laoreet at.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ELECTRODE: Electrode position for cardioversion</title>
      <link>/project/electrode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/electrode/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
