<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Anders Sjørslev Schmidt</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Anders Sjørslev Schmidt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Can we predict cardioversion outcomes using copeptin?</title>
      <link>/post/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sample/</guid>
      <description>CopeptinText happens here.
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug repurposing: A talk by James Harrison, Cycle Pharma</title>
      <link>/post/drug-repurposing-a-talk-by-james-harrison-cycle-pharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/drug-repurposing-a-talk-by-james-harrison-cycle-pharma/</guid>
      <description>James Harrison is excecutive chairman of Cycle Pharmaceuticals, a company based on an exiting idea: Using well-known mediccations for new purposes &amp;ldquo;re-purposing&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tableone package: Effiencent Table 1&#39;s for clinical studies</title>
      <link>/post/the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-tableone-package-effiencent-table-1-s-for-clinical-studies/</guid>
      <description>Every randomized study need a Table 1 to summarize the characteristics of the included participants. The tables consist of multiple calculations of means with standard deviation, medians with quartiles or summarizes of categorical variables. This can however be very time consuming to calculate if done by hard. Especially, because you often want to make several subgroups etc.
Some years ago I came across the R package tableone, which has now become my preffered tool for creating table 1’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Descion-tree analysis: A look on the FFTrees package</title>
      <link>/post/descion-tree-analysis-a-look-on-the-fftrees-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/descion-tree-analysis-a-look-on-the-fftrees-package/</guid>
      <description>As medical doctors we use descions tree every day. Many observations from studies have been condensed to a clinical scoring system which aid the clinican in taking descions about further investigations on a given patient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My notes on - Effect size and sample size estimations for clinical trials</title>
      <link>/post/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sample/</guid>
      <description>On my way to design a third and fourth clinical trial I found it useful to reflect on the way the previous studies were designed and what considerations I have made. Randomized trials are only as good as they are designed - and important considerations must be made prior to the initiation of the project. Often recruitment of patients may last for years and therefore a careful plan is needed to enhance the scientific outcome of the study.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>